leandrosavat@gmail.com / Argentina / (+54) 3435267411 / DNI 35295349 / Links: ( ) [ 0 ] [ in









# LEANDRO JOSE OSCAR SAVAT.["letsHelp"][the].world()

### UNIVERSITY EXPERT IN WEB ENGINEERING

W Hello! I am Leandro, University Expert in Web Engineering with more than 11 years of experience in planning and developing personal and business image.

★My greatest achievement has been founding an image development company, delegating activities and expanding my services to Community Manager in Hostels in Europe and Africa, which has allowed us to increase the level of English and the multicultural appreciation of users.

My dream is to be a Technical Product Manager and apply my skills, empathy and ideas together with a powerful team to create products that optimize people's lives.

#### **EXPERIENCES**

- → From Nov 2022 : Web Engineering Expert.
  - Freelance. Web Application Programming.
- $\rightarrow$  2021-2022 : **Developer Analyst**.

Statistical analysis and development of trend indicators.

- $\rightarrow$  2019-2021 : Community Manager.
  - Image production and management of social networks for Hostels in Europe and Africa.
- → From 2010: **Development and Design** of personal and business image at SAVAT Producciones. Client contact, profile analysis, idea research, personal team coordination, photography, graphic design.
- → 2008-2010 : Cyber **Software Technician.** Computer hardware and software management.

## **PROJECTS**

- Savat: Frontend Portfolio → React / Context / JavaScript / HTML / CSS
- Bcryptis / JWT / Hacking Inputs Sanitize / API REST / MongoDb Atlas / Express

- ⑤ Innovation: Front-end Landing Page → React / JavaScript / HTML / Styled Components / Figma

#### **EDUCATION**

→ 01-07/2022 - 13/07/2023 UNIVERSITY EXPERT IN WEB SITE ENGINEERING + Bootcamps.

Technological University of Mexico + Henry + Openbootcamp + FreecodeCamp.

→ 2019-2021 : **ENGLISH**.

Step English language institute / Oral Internship on a global trip.

 $\rightarrow$  2007-2010 : **UTN University.** 

Engineering student in Information Systems.

Skills → { Web Engineering, Full Stack, Product Design, UI-UX Design, Front End React, Back End , Analyst Developer, Scrum }

Technologies → { Excel, Notion, Photoshop, Lightroom, CaptureOne, Figma, Wordpress, Visual Studio Code, Git, Javascript, HTML, CSS, React, Node.js, Express, JWT, Zustand, MongoDb, Postman }